Guide to the Leonard Eugene Root Papers, 1923-1983
Department of Special Collections
- Series 9: BOOKS
  - Gardner, John W. We. The People. Pasadena, CA: California Institute of Technology, 1968. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Gibson, A.H. Osborne Reynolds. London: Longmans, Green and Co. Ltd., 1948. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Gossett, William T. Corporate Citizenship. Lexington, VA: Washington and Lee University, 1957. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Guggenheim Aeronautical Laboratory. GALCIT. The First Twenty-Five Years. Pasadena, CA: California Institute of Technology, 1954. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Hildred, Sir William. Administrative Aspects of International Air Transport. New York: The Wings Club, 1967. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Lapp, Ralph E. Space Science. New York: Public Affairs Pamphlets, 1962. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - LeGalley, Donald P. Ballistic Missiles and Space Technology. New York: Academic Press, 1960. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Mesthene, Emmanuel G. How Technology Will Shape the Future. Cambridge, MA: Harvard University, 1968. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - National Rifle Association. Training Course Organization. Washington D.C.: NRA, 1955. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Newell, Homer E. NASA's Space Science and Applications Program. Washington, D.C.: NASA, 1967. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Raymond, Arthur E. A Gentleman of the Old School. Pasadena, CA: Pasadena Historical Society, 1982. (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - The Third Dr. Albert Plesman Memorial Lecture. DELFT, 6 October. 1959. (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - United States Advisory Commission on Information. Twenty-Second Report. 1967. (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - United States Air Force. Air University Quarterly. Vol XI, Number 2, 1959. (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - United States Naval Academy. Annapolis. n.d. (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Wohlstetter, Albert. No Highway to High Purpose. Santa Monica, CA: (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Yearbooks: The Najarando College of The Pacific, 1929-1935 (Box 23)
  - Yearbooks: The Najarando College of The Pacific, 1929-1935 (Box 24)